[choir singing liturgical music]
[girl] My whole life,
I've dreamt about being dead.
I leave my body,
and I see myself from above.
A normal girl, just... normal.
I stare at her perfect normality
until I wake up
and realize that I'm still the freak
I've been my whole life.
One thing I've learned since then...
life has a really fucked-up way
of making your dreams come true.
[man] Tragic.
Such a young and pleasant face.
The Devil may present a pleasing visage.
The better to seduce and influence
the weak-minded.
I see. So she was--
She will burn like those who spawned her.
[monk] You assume she is in Hell?
It wouldn't matter.
She was in Hell already.
Well, name,
age, cause of death for the book.
Ava Silva, 19.
-Leave the cause of death blank.
-I'm not supposed to--
I said leave it blank.
[sighs] As you wish.
[phone beeps, buzzes]
[sighs]
Forgive me, Sister,
but I have to ask you to leave now
so I can attend to some urgent matters.
But please remember,
she cannot ask for forgiveness anymore,
so it's up to us to forgive her.
For God knows all and sees all
and will be thy judge.
I'll take my chances.
[dog barking in distance]
[clattering echoes]
[slams loudly]
[woman 1] Monk!
I need somewhere to put her down.
[monk] Sister Shannon. Over here.
[grunting]
[sword clatters]
[woman 2 panting] Mary.
[Mary] Easy.
We're here.
[woman 3] I've got the surgeon.
Divinium shrapnel.
You gotta get it all out
before it kills her.
[screams]
-How bad is it?
-Let her work, Lilith.
You're strong, girl.
You're gonna pull through.
Get the pieces out so she can heal.
Your organs are pierced.
Liver, spleen.
Several of these shards
are keeping you from bleeding out.
If I remove them, it could kill her.
-Can you give her something for the pain?
-[woman 2 coughing]
We've seen worse, haven't we?
Mary.
Don't say it, Lilith.
Don't even think about it.
You think I want this? It's not up to us.
There's a protocol.
[loud bang]
[distant automatic gunfire]
-Sounds like the fight followed us here.
-Six targets incoming.
-The other Sisters will hold them off.
-Not for long.
-[automatic gunfire rattling]
-Mary. You know what needs to happen.
Beatrice, get her out of here
before I shoot her.
She's right.
This is Shannon.
She is our leader. She's our friend.
We are not gonna give up on her.
Mary, I'm not gonna make it.
Take it out.
-[gun clicks]
-No!
-[grunts]
-[chain snaps]
[Shannon] Take it.
Mary.
[sighs]
[whimpering]
In this life or the next.
[loud slamming]
They've broken through.
-[Lilith] I'll buy us time.
-You're needed here.
[men shouting in distance]
[Beatrice] I'll miss you, Sister.
[automatic gunfire rattling]
[door opens]
I'm sorry, Shannon.
You're ready.
We both know it.
[woman] We need to turn her over.
[Shannon moaning]
[Mary] Shh, shh, shh.
Keep it safe,
or all will be lost.
Mary?
Yes?
Mary.
Yeah.
Don't...
trust...
Who?
[clacking]
[Shannon grunts]
Who?
...anyone.
[crackling]
[clacking, sizzling]
[high-pitched ringing]
[speaking Spanish]
Oh, it is beautiful, Shannon.
It's beautiful.
Are you the next Bearer?
No.
-Lilith--
-[exploding]
[women grunting, screaming]
[debris clattering]
[men shouting in distance]
[gun clicks]
[men shouting in Spanish]
[automatic gunfire rattling]
[women screaming, grunting]
[clattering]
-[high-pitched ringing]
-[sizzling]
[man screaming]
Forgive me, child.
[sizzling]
[automatic gunfire rattling in distance]
[both grunt]
[thuds]
-[woman screaming]
-[man grunting]
-[shrieks]
-[grunts]
[thuds]
[grunting]
[automatic gunfire continues]
[pounding]
[gasping, screaming]
-[distant sinister laughter]
-[indistinct voices chattering]
[echoing]
All right, child, it's time for your walk.
-[Ava giggles] That tickles, Sister.
-You think that's funny?
[woman] See? He's dying over there.
[nun]
She will burn like those who spawned her.
[monk] You assume she's in Hell.
[nun] It doesn't matter.
[indistinct chatter]
[woman laughing]
[voices grunting, chattering]
[nun] She was in Hell already.
[laughing]
[voices grunting, chattering]
[nun's voice] Could you at least try
to be anything but a burden
on everyone around you?
-[echoing] The poor child has left us.
-[child laughing]
The poor child has left us.
[shrieks]
[gasping, screaming]
[man grunts, thuds]
[panting]
[woman grunting in distance]
[groans]
[grunts]
[woman grunting, struggling]
[man grunts]
[woman continues grunting]
[moaning]
[automatic gunfire rattling]
[panting]
[grunting]
-[man grunts]
-[blow thuds]
[man grunts]
[panting, moaning]
[grunting]
[creature roars]
[air hissing]
The fuck?
[Ava panting]
[creature moaning, screeching]
[grunts] No!
[creature continues moaning, screeching]
[screams]
[growling, screeching]
-[gasps]
-[automatic gunfire rattling]
[clattering]
[panting]
-[rapid gunfire]
-[moaning]
[automatic gunfire continues]
This is not a dream.
[panting]
[high-pitched ringing]
[gong sounds]
[panting]
[Ava's voice] Are we gonna talk about
what happened back there?
No.
That shit was a bad trip,
and it can't be real.
That's just you coming down
from some powerful drugs.
Gotta be.
Better be.
["Ilomilo" by Billie Eilish playing]
♪ Told you not to worry ♪
♪ But maybe that's a lie ♪
♪ Honey, what's your hurry? ♪
[Ava's voice]
Maybe I'm dead, and this is Hell.
♪ Won't you stay inside... ♪
The nuns at the orphanage
always said I was a good candidate.
At least here my legs work,
so fuck those old crows.
If this is Hell,
then I'm gonna do it right.
♪ Like ours ♪
♪ Where did you go?
I should know, but it's cold... ♪
[music fades]
[distant siren blaring]
[Ava's voice]
Maybe this is what going crazy feels like.
I'm probably back in my bed
at the orphanage,
and all of this
is just happening in my imagination.
And I have completely lost my mental shit
so bad, I have no idea.
And my brain is protecting me by making
all of this seem really fucking real
to distract me from the fact
that I'm a complete basket case.
[laughing]
[speaking Spanish]
[continues laughing] What? What? What?
Ooh. Nice outfit!
You drunk?
No, but I might be dead.
[grunts] What is this?
What?
I-- I don't feel so...
[gagging, retching]
[man] Yo, what the...
[Ava]
Oh, my God. I'm sorry. That's so gro--
[Ava grunting]
[groans]
[loud thud]
[Ava grunting, panting]
-[high-pitched ringing]
-Fuck.
[grunts]
[Ava's voice] Goddamn.
[high-pitched ringing continues]
[Ava's voice] Okay, this isn't a dream.
This is hardcore real life.
[whimpers]
[gasping]
With superpowers?
Something has definitely changed.
What are you up to, God?
[grunts]
[panting]
Oh, I really hope this team doesn't suck.
The nuns used to talk about miracles.
Well, they were full of shit.
But what if they weren't?
I'm not sure I'm ready to handle that.
I don't look any different.
At least I don't think I do.
To be honest, I've never really spent
any time looking at myself.
Never had the chance.
[chuckles]
Hi, Ava.
[kisses]
[laughing]
I know I should be grateful.
A lot of people would kill to have
this sort of thing happen to them.
But you can't blame me for being confused.
There's gotta be a reason
this is happening.
Someone did this to you,
and that someone must have answers.
[distant bell tolling]
-[siren blaring]
-[police radio chattering]
It was a rough first assignment.
But you did well, Camila.
Thanks.
You don't have to do that.
We can reassemble these fragments.
If we find out what holy relic did this,
we can trace it.
Never alone, never forgotten,
ever in our spirits.
May I?
[priest] Tell me what happened.
[Beatrice] They followed us
back here, Father. Engaged us.
[priest]
No, before this. The recovery mission.
Your assignment.
[Beatrice] There was more resistance
than we expected.
And by "resistance,"
she means a private army.
Armed mercenaries
were at the delivery location.
We secured the area,
but when we went to retrieve the item,
there was a detonation.
Divinium mixed with explosives.
Sister Shannon was critically wounded,
so we pulled back
to our secondary position.
-But they followed us--
-[Mary] Stop doing that.
This is Shannon.
You are talking like
it's just another incident to report.
I'm sorry, Mary.
I loved her, too.
I just...
need something to focus on.
[priest] What about the other
Divinium fragments at the dock?
We need to secure them before
someone else gets their hands on them.
I'll handle it.
[footsetps approaching]
Is Lilith ready?
Father Vincent,
the monk has something to show us.
I hid after we were attacked.
And then she came in with El Halo
and put it inside a dead body
to keep it safe.
Here.
She was here.
What do you mean?
There was a corpse.
The body of a young girl.
Why would she do that?
Human skin and tissue
dampen the Halo's unique energy signature.
Makes it difficult to locate.
Unless its power is unleashed.
The girl, who was she?
Has it ever done that before,
brought someone back?
Not that I'm aware.
You're saying some random,
formerly dead civilian is out there
with an angel's Halo inside her?
Perhaps not entirely random.
[crickets chirping]
[sighs]
[women chatting indistinctly]
[boy] Are you an angel?
Ava?
I think so.
You're-- you're walking.
You-- you're walking.
[Ava laughing] Yeah.
But-- but how?
You're not...
You-- you died.
Weirdly, that makes sense.
When, Diego?
[Diego] Yesterday.
You went to sleep, and you never woke up.
They took you away.
Is this a dream?
[Ava] No.
No. I thought so, too.
I'm really here.
I'm alive. [chuckles]
But I'm different.
I feel strong.
[exhales]
I think I have superpowers.
-Cool.
-Yeah.
My body can heal itself.
I can move through walls...
sometimes.
[scoffs]
What's happening to me?
Maybe some kind of delayed zombification.
Um, or your consciousness
got transferred into another host body.
Or you're a clone
in some horrible experiment.
Whatever it is,
you can't let anyone here
see you like this.
Yeah. The Catholics are a little twitchy
about who gets to be resurrected.
Unless they control the narrative.
Why do you want to know about her?
I'm following up an inquiry.
From whom?
I can't say.
The girl's family perhaps?
We were under the impression
there was none.
I don't want to get into the details,
Sister.
The girl is dead, as you said.
This is simply an attempt to gather
information for a concerned party.
Well, yes, but if I knew--
I'm on official Vatican business.
At the highest levels.
I don't have a lot of time.
I don't know, Ava.
This whole thing could just be temporary,
like a glitch in the matrix.
If I were you, I'd make the most of it
while you still can
before whoever did this to you finds you.
I'll fetch the girl's files.
Thank you.
And any information you might have
on her friends...
or places she used to frequent.
I don't understand, Father.
Ava never left the building,
and she certainly didn't have any friends.
That seems odd.
It's not odd at all.
You do know she was a quadriplegic?
[door opens]
[nun] Diego!
-What are you doing awake at this hour?
-There was a pájaro.
A bird.
It's gone now.
Not exactly
twenty-first-century care here, is it?
We do the best with the limited resources
we are given, Father.
Were you and Ava good friends, Diego?
Sí, Padre.
You must miss her.
Sí.
Very much.
She seems like a special girl.
She is... was.
[waves crashing]
[indistinct music blaring in distance]
[ship horn blaring]
["They Ran" by Message to Bears playing]
♪ When we talked about
Where we'd go ♪
♪ Never thought of how
How we'd run ♪
♪ When we talked about
Where we'd go ♪
[screams]
♪ Never thought of how
How we'd run ♪
♪ When we talked about
Where we'd go ♪
♪ Never thought of how
How we'd run ♪
[crying]
[vocalizing]
[Ava's voice] I promise you, Diego,
I'm gonna make the most of this.
[high-pitched snarling]
[Ava's voice] And just when you feel like
you got this whole situation in hand,
you see this shit.
And it draws you
like a helpless insect into a flame.
[air hissing]
You follow, even though
you know it's a bad idea.
[women chattering indistinctly]
[indistinct music playing in distance]
["I Follow Rivers" by Lykke Li playing]
♪ Run deep, run wild ♪
♪ I, I follow ♪
♪ I follow you deep sea baby ♪
♪ I follow you ♪
♪ I, I follow ♪
♪ I follow you deep sea baby ♪
♪ I follow you ♪
♪ I, I follow ♪
♪ I follow you
Dark room, honey ♪
♪ I follow you... ♪
Hey.
[Ava] Hi.
Do you want some?
Sure.
[gags]
That's alcohol!
Are you sober?
Well, not on purpose!
Hey! No spitting!
No spinning?
[laughs]
Spitting!
-There! On the floor--
-[blow thuds]
-[man grunts]
-[Ava screams]
[glass shattering]
Shit! Sorry!
[patrons murmur]
[Ava gasping]
Ah!
Thank you.
I should probably go.
Bye.
How did Ava come to find herself
at the orphanage, Sister?
Ava was only seven years old
when she came to us.
She was already broken.
The result of a horrible car accident
that took the life of her poor mother.
God rest her soul.
They were here on holiday.
[clicks tongue]
She didn't know her father,
and there was no other family
that we could find.
But given that the mother was a Catholic,
the child was placed in our care.
She was a difficult girl.
Ungrateful.
I would like to say
that she will be missed, but...
[priest] One more question, Sister.
How did Ava die?
[Ava's voice] So tired,
but I can't go to sleep.
What if I wake up
and I'm back to the way I was?
No, I gotta stay awake.
There's still so much to do.
So many firsts to experience.
Yeah.
Cold water.
Shock to the senses.
This will do it.
Wait. Do my God powers include swimming?
Because I just realized...
I can't swim.
Fuck!
[screams] Help!
Help!
[gasps, screams]
Hold on! Hold on!
[Ava screaming]
I got you! I got you!
It's okay. I got you.
[Ava gasping]
Are you okay?
[Ava's voice] Saved by a cute boy.
Check that one off the list.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm JC.
[Ava's voice] Now try to focus, Ava.
Don't do that thing
where you forget to speak.
I'm-- I'm hungry.
Hungry?
Ava. I'm Ava. Sorry.
Okay, Hungry Ava.
I can fix that.
[Ava chuckles]
Mmm.
Wow, you weren't kidding.
-[door creaks]
-Yeah.
[women chuckling]
[JC] Oh, long night?
Uh, so, this is Chanel, Zori, and Randall.
Mmm--
Hey.
Hello.
Okay. [sighs]
[gulps] Nice to meet you.
Who are you?
Nobody.
I'm Ava. [clears throat]
Where are you from, Ava Nobody?
Just...
here and there.
Around.
How very obtuse.
What?
It means you're a mystery.
Come on. She's a mystery.
We all love a good mystery, don't we?
[birds squawking]
The truth is, some people
might be looking for me right now,
so I'm happy to keep a low profile.
Where are you staying?
Um...
Wait, is this your house?
-No.
-Don't worry so much about who owns what.
Just enjoy the view.
[scoffs]
I mean, it's not like
you're squatting here or something.
[motorcycle engine revving]
[swords clacking]
[people grunting]
[bell tolling]
Do we know who was at the docks?
Why they were receiving
a shipment of Divinium?
Not yet.
Let's distribute this
to the entire diocese.
I want every priest, deacon,
and nun in Andalusia
on the lookout for her.
[Mary] What happened to Shannon?
Divinium exploding into her,
ripping her to pieces.
This is how you kill a Warrior Nun.
And they knew we were coming.
Why else would there be mercenaries
waiting for us?
That has never happened before.
What's changed?
I don't know.
All the more reason
to find the Halo quickly.
Its power in someone untrained, untested,
or unworthy is a danger to us all.
So, I find her, then what?
The Halo brought her back.
Will removing it kill her?
That's why you called me.
You need someone who's okay with that.
I need someone I can trust.
Lilith is driven by ambition.
Beatrice is brilliant but guarded.
You are who I rely on.
Who I've always relied on.
[birds squawking]
-Hey.
-[JC] Hey.
I can stay here?
Oh, uh...
Well, not forever,
but a few nights for sure.
We tend to keep a busy schedule.
Italy, France...
Wherever the action is.
Yeah, something like that.
So, um, why are people looking for you?
Uh...
Hey, you want to take a walk on the beach?
Sure.
So, you're criminals.
We're opportunists.
What's the difference?
Well, we're not taking anything
that isn't already being offered up
for free.
Hmm.
That beach house?
The owner lives in Saudi Arabia.
They come to Spain once or twice a year.
The rest of the time it sits empty.
They don't rent it out.
They don't Airbnb it.
So we pop in, we use it for a few weeks,
we get it professionally cleaned
before the owners return.
And, yeah.
I don't know.
Nobody gets hurt. Life is good.
Look, the system is rigged
against people like us
getting money, nice houses.
They-- they say if you work hard,
you can get everything, etc., etc.
But that's a lie. Okay?
You gotta be in one of the...
[Ava's voice]
Just keep talking, pretty boy.
I don't care what you're talking about.
I just see lips I wanna kiss.
I understand.
You do?
Yeah.
Institutions.
[scoffs] I hate them.
You know, they focus power
in one direction,
and everyone under them is just abused.
Yeah, that's right. We're pushing back.
-Yeah.
-Making the most.
-We're trying to.
Can I help?
[JC] Sure. Yes.
The more the merrier.
Okay.
There's just something
that you need to know.
You're Interpol?
[laughs]
No. [giggles]
Um...
I'm sort of new-- new to this.
I don't have a lot of life experience.
So, I may need your help
to figure some stuff out.
I mean, not help.
Okay, I'm a strong woman.
I don't need your help.
It's not like, "Oh, help," you know?
It's just a little help.
I do realize that I keep saying
that word again. Help. And...
-I just said it again. I did it again.
-[laughs]
But did you just say anything?
No?
I got you.
What are you doing?
[laughs] I'm-- I'm wondering
what I'm going to wear tonight.
What's tonight?
Big party.
There's a dance rave at the prison.
At the pris-- Like a real prison,
or a club called the Prison?
A real prison,
once upon a time.
Cool.
I'm sorry about earlier today.
We were in rough shape.
Strangers tend to make us
a bit uncomfortable.
Yeah, no.
No problem. It's fine.
Hey, I think this could look
really great on you.
I can do some minor alterations.
Really? I-- I trust you. Yeah.
[laughs] Oh, my God.
Good decision.
[dance music playing]
Yeah.
[dance music grows louder]
♪ Let's go ♪
Fucking epic.
[dance music continues]
Hey!
Can I have one?
Are you sure?
No.
Yeah?
[bell tolling in distance]
[playing minor piano music]
[jangles]
[piano music continues]
[women grunting]
[Mary] You okay?
[Shannon] Yeah, why?
[Mary] Normally, you kick my ass
in sparring and don't break a sweat.
Normally, you enjoy it.
Today-- today, you were fighting
something else while you were fighting me.
-Something's on your mind.
-I'm working it out.
I respectfully disagree.
Come on. Give me something.
I know it's not me. I'm a goddamn gift.
-Language.
-Oh, bullshit.
You know I love you, right?
And I love all the girls here.
Yeah, I know.
You protect the ones you love.
And I'm protecting you.
And I'm protecting them.
I know this doesn't make
much sense right now, but...
it will some point in the future.
Trust me.
Okay.
Just remember that we love you, too.
[continues playing minor piano music]
♪ That's the way every day goes ♪
♪ Every time we've got no control ♪
♪ If the sky is pink and white ♪
♪ If the ground is black and yellow ♪
♪ It's the same way you showed me ♪
♪ Nod my head, don't close my eyes ♪
♪ Halfway on a slow move ♪
♪ Just the same way you showed me ♪
♪ If... ♪
Come join us, Father.
[priest chuckles]
Thank you, Camila,
but I have somewhere to be.
[sniffles]
♪ If you could fly
Then you'd feel south ♪
♪ Up north's getting cold soon ♪
♪ Just the same way you showed me ♪
♪ You showed me ♪
♪ You showed me love ♪
[sniffles]
[dance music playing]
[vocalizing]
♪ I want you and you want me, too ♪
Are you okay?
Yeah. I-- I gotta pee.
Be right back.
♪ I want you and you want me, too ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ I want you and you want me, too
I want you and you want me, too ♪
[whirring]
[whirring continues]
[bartender in Spanish]
Would you like water with that, Father?
[in Spanish] No, I'm not drinking it.
Just looking at it.
I understand.
You know...
Sometimes... it helps to share
what's on your mind.
You and I have the same job.
Listening.
So... Come on. [knocks]
[priest, in Spanish] How do I explain?
What if I told you that Demons were real?
That they were among us?
[air hissing]
[priest continues]
Some are...
ethereal monsters that feed off our souls
and push us to do evil.
[whooshing]
[whooshing, moaning]
[screeching]
[wailing]
[priest] Others are beasts from Hell
that could slice you in half
with a single swipe of their claw.
[clanking, clattering]
-[snarling, screeching]
-[slashing]
[priest] You would nod
your head and say you understand,
because I'm a priest.
You expect me to say these things.
Things that might be metaphorical
and not literal.
[no audible dialogue]
[priest]
But what if I weren't a priest?
What if I told you all this as a layman?
You would think that either
I was a madman or a prophet.
And these days,
it's very hard to believe in prophets.
[snarling]
[creature screeching, roaring]
[vocalizing]